

VICTOR SVETAILO

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT













CONTACT



Phone

+7 962 007 05 55



Fmail

victorsvetailo@gmail.com



Address

Turkey Antalya 07040



EDUCATION

 $(\mathbf{2})$ IT-Incubator 2022



Frontend developer. (React/Redux/TypeScript)

Freelancer for life link \odot 2020 - 2021





Creating websites Course. HTML, CSS (SCSS), JS

WAY UP & Gavrilov \odot



HTML - CSS, Wordpress Bootstrap Course.



LANGUAGE

Native

Pre-Intermediate English in progress

Temel 2 Turkish



ABOUT ME

Hello everyone. I'm Front-End developer with experience and good knowledge in creating SPA using React, Redux, Typescript, JS, HTML, and CSS. Almost every day I improve my skills. I'm planning to study Node.is because my next focus is to become a Full-Stack Developer. I would like to find a job in a creative company with up-to-date tasks and a collaborative team! Open for your suggestions!



MY SKILLS & EXPERTISE

- JavaScript / TypeScriptUnitTest / Jest / TDD

React

- StoryBook / Postman
- Redux / Redux-Toolkit
- Formik / Redux Form
- Rest API / Axios
- Ant Design / Material UI
- HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS
- Git/GitHub



WORK EXPERIENCE

() EnglishShow @ link Online IT School 2021 - 2022 KodKodych A link

Mentor. HR. Development of programming courses.

December 2021 - present day

Full time.

Stack: HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS, JavaScript, React, Scratch

TRAINING CARDS. GitHub link



November 2022 - present day Start-up project, Part time

Stack: TypeScript, React, Redux, Redux-thunk, React-Router-Dom, Axios, Formik, Material-UI. Using TypeScript for better code control, ESLint, Prettier for the best code style. Organizing correct app arcitecture. Team development: bug fixing, refactoring, deploying.

TODO LIST GitHub link



July 2022 - November 2022

Start-up project, Part time

Stack: TypeScript, React, Redux, Redux-thunk, React-Router-Dom, Axios, Material-UI. Using TypeScript for better code control. Covering code with unit tests, bug fixing, refactoring, deploying.

SOCIAL NETWORK GitHub link



February 2022 - September 2022

Start-up project, Part time

Stack: TypeScript, React, Redux, Redux-thunk, React-Router-Dom, Axios, Redux-form, Ant Design, Reselect. Using TypeScript for better code control, ESLint, Prettier for the best code style. Creating unit tests, bug fixing, refactoring, deploying. Organizing correct app arcitecture.

Online IT School (>) HelloWorld | link 2020 - 2022

TEACHER OF PROGRAMMING COURSES

December 2020 - January 2022 Full time.

Stack: HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS, JavaScript, Lua, Scratch

(2016 - 2020) Own business in the field of online stores.